WHY?!
I DON'T UNDERSTAND!
The boss truly is a fierce foe.
Why? Why?!
Well? What'd she screw up this time?
No, no...
Thea did nothing wrong.
That's right!
My plan was impeccable!
When Teach was walking around town,
we waited until he was in front of the hotel.
By all rights, he should have been worried
about Grete and taken her inside.
That's just what men do!
And yet...
Why are you soaking wet?
He simply left like he'd seen right through us.
That's a first-rate spy for you.
He never lets down his guard.
What a formidable opponent.
Look, can I ask you a question?
What?
I've been wondering this for a while now,
but are you sure you're any good at seduction?
Excuse me?!
Me wo aketa kikkake wa
Kokoro saku joukei
Hirari hirari yubi no sukima kara
Mietekuru shinjitsu wo nirame
Kizukareta no wa, rakuen?
Massakasama ochite
Aa tatoe kouya demo
Hitori de ikiru to oritachimashou
Ikanakucha
Koko ni aru hana wa ima eien nare to
Gokujou no chihedo wo haite watashi ga ueta mono
Kono koe de ashi de te de watashi no mama mogaku hodo ni
Doushiyou mo nai sekai ga itoshii
Tadoritsuku wa kanarazu
Musekaeru hodo no yume
FILE: Dreamspeaker Thea
How utterly humiliating!
How dare Monika even say that?!
You're young, you've got an erotic figure,
and you come across as an easy lay.
You've got the kind of looks that idiot dudes
go crazy for, that's all.
Pressing your massive tits against some ape to get him
hot and bothered so you can manipulate him
hardly requires a professional.
No, no, she's just a contrarian.
Surely, the others all revere me
as an expert in matters of romance.
But now that I think about it...
that might just be because none of them are proactive
about matters of the heart themselves.
Honestly, Lamplight is so full of people who
shy away from romance, it's almost worrying.
Come in.
You mind helpin' out here?
You're the only one we can turn to.
You got a love letter?
That's right.
What kind of person is he?
So...
Sara was playin' with Johnny
at a pet shop in the capital,
and this guy gave the letter to one of the
employees to pass along to her.
"I fell for you at first sight."
"From, Dominic Maura."
And? How did you reply?
I wrote a letter back turning him down.
I was happy he felt that way,
but my schedule's just too full.
That's when these started comin'.
Wow! What passion!
What a stalker, is more like it.
To be honest, it's gotten to be so much that
I feel awkward even going to the pet shop anymore.
And Mr. Johnny used to love it there so much...
What should I do?
So, Sara, you haven't actually met
this Dominic yet, right?
No, we've only exchanged letters.
Why not try meeting up with him, then?
But I'm a spy!
Forget about that for a moment.
What do you want?
Do you want to give dating a chance?
I, um...
There's actually someone who I think is lovely...
For real?!
B-but I'm not sure if that's actually love or not.
I think I might be enamored with
the idea of being in love.
That it would be nice to fall for someone
the way Miss Grete did.
At your age, that's completely normal.
Sounds like it's settled, then.
Go out and meet Dominic.
If nothing else, it will help you figure out
if what you're feeling really is love.
I think you're super cute, yo!
You look wonderful, Big Sis Sara.
Yeah, the outfit's great.
Thea picked out a real winner!
I should certainly think so.
You never disappoint, Master Thea!
Damn, good going.
I'll be your backup, Sara,
so make sure you take your radio along with you.
Wait, you're going to be watching me?!
With all of us working together,
we'll be able to orchestrate the best date ever.
Yeah!
Ugh, what a bunch of busybodies.
Oh, you're not coming?
I'm only gonna stick around until midmorning.
So, you are coming after all.
Don't you worry.
If he pulls any funny business,
I'll punch him into next week.
I'm getting butterflies now, too.
I've got the radios all up and working, yo.
This is good.
I hope you don't mind if I use this as reference
for planning a date with the boss.
I knew they were interested in romance.
I hope you don't mind if I use this as reference
for planning a date with the boss.
I knew they were interested in romance.
I'm rooting for you.
"I'm off to watch over Lamplight's adolescences."
So, they all went out together?
I'm not sure I follow, but it's nice that they're
taking a breather every now and again.
Magnificent.
I've got a clear visual on the rendezvous site, yo!
There's no danger in the area.
So far, so good.
And remember, what do we do if the guy is a dirtbag
who tries to get handsy with Sara?
Blow him up.
Get him caught up in one of my accidents.
That seems a little excessive.
It sounds as though we're getting good reception.
Damn, that place is crowded.
So, it's a café you can go into with your pets, huh?
Pets are all the rage right now.
I hear that they're super popular
with the rich and famous.
I am a bit worried.
To be honest, Sara comes across as timid,
and that sort of thing can attract some real weirdos.
For sure.
I have visual on the target!
Someone came up and started talking to Big Sis Sara!
He's got beige pants.
A black jacket.
A lily-of-the-valley bouquet.
Bronze-colored hair!
That must be him.
Gulp...
He's a total hunk!
I'm so sorry.
I probably made a complete nuisance of myself,
sending you all those letters.
Oh, no, um...
I'm thinking of getting a dog myself,
and as I was walking around the pet shop,
I happened to spot you,
and, well, I fell for you at first sight.
Th-that's very kind of you to say.
As for me, I'm a senior at Shalita University.
I study genetically modified crops.
Have you heard of Weyrich corn?
It's incredibly nutritious,
so it's great to feed to your pets.
Actually, do you know of any food that
would be good for a hawk's health?
Mine's been a little under the weather lately.
A hawk, huh?
I'll have to ask the professor next time I see him.
You mean, one of the teachers at your university?
No, Professor Tott.
I met him at a conference last month,
and we really hit it off.
Isn't he one of the biggest names in biology?
That's incredible!
This is boring, I'm gonna bail.
Besides, it feels rude to keep eavesdropping like this.
Agreed.
Well, we came all the way to the capital.
We should grab some sweets
before we head on back!
Ooh, sold.
I would love to join you!
Let's do this!
Yeah!
I'm so excited.
Yeah, I'm starvin'.
Ooh, how does getting pancakes sound?
The date looks like it's going swimmingly.
It seems as though they're going to
keep getting closer,
so I should check him, just in case.
Goodness, is that you?
Oh, it's been so long!
Have you been keeping well?
N-not to be rude, but who are you?
Oh, I'm so sorry.
I mistook you for someone else!
I-I see.
Goodbye, then.
The desire I saw in that man...
FILE: Dreamspeaker Thea
You did great today.
Oh, Miss Thea!
Shall we walk while we chat?
My heart was beating a mile a minute back there.
Oh yeah?
Well, how was it?
What do you think of Dominic?
I haven't finished getting all my emotions in order yet,
but I really just don't know.
Still, it made me happy when he called me cute,
but it's also really embarrassing.
People don't tell me that all that often.
Look, Sara...
There's something I need to tell-
You got a sec?
I looked up every student currently
enrolled at Shalita University.
There isn't a single senior that goes there
named Dominic Maura.
Plus, there weren't any students involved
in developing Weyrich corn,
and Professor Tott was on an
international research trip all last month,
so he didn't go to any conferences.
Wh-what do you mean?
Dominic just told me-
His real name is Tarik Pupke.
He got arrested last month.
Truth is, he runs romance scams.
He's a con artist?
That can't be!
He targets younger girls without
much romantic experience.
Once he starts a relationship with them,
he pretends to be hard up for cash
and gets them to steal jewelry
and stuff from their parents.
But if he got arrested just last month,
then why is he free now?
And why would he go after someone like me
without any valuables?
Sybilla and Grete are tailing him as we speak.
He just went into a pub with some friends.
You got it in you to listen in on their conversation?
I'm telling you, it's hilarious how naïve this kid is.
Once I get her to fall for me, I'll snatch up her dog.
Rich people will pay through the nose
for a puppy that well-trained.
After that, it won't matter what she says.
Once again, there won't be enough
evidence to prosecute.
Man, what a joke.
What guy in his right mind would ever
fall for a bumpkin like her?
Don't worry, Sara.
He's about to experience a fate worse than death.
Yeah!
Anyone who toys with Sara's feelings
like that is dead meat.
Pl-please, stop!
I-it's fine.
You don't have to do that.
And why not?
I was being stupid.
I would have realized, if I'd thought about it.
I should have figured out it was a con
the moment someone said
they'd fallen for someone like me!
Sara!
Was that stuff just now true?
Is Dominic really a conman?
Y'know...
I think I'm gonna go for a nice little stroll, yo.
I'm coming with you.
Hold it.
Don’t get in our way.
We need to teach that guy that there are
some people you just don't mess with.
That's not what I'm doing.
I'm saying that I have a better way to settle this.
I'm code name Dreamspeaker,
and it's time to lure them to their ruin.
Grete, could you make an outfit
that matches this drawing?
On it!
Lily and Erna, help me whip up some perfume.
Will do!
Sybilla, I'm sorry to have to ask this,
but would you mind running out and
getting us the materials we need?
Leave it to me.
Annette, your job is to compile me
a list of Far East restaurants.
Roger that, yo!
Monika, continue keeping tabs on Tarik's location.
Sure.
This isn't just Sara's problem anymore.
Our pride is on the line here,
so let's make this mission a success.
Yeah!
I'm so sorry I got you all wrapped up in this.
Not at all.
If anyone needs to apologize, it's me.
I'm sorry.
But if I can offer an excuse,
I wanted to show you something.
I wanted you to see what a charming girl you are,
and that you're just as qualified and have as much
right as anyone to experience romance.
I wanted the entire team to realize
that about themselves.
Miss Thea...
Matters of romance need to be settled with romance.
I'm done messing around.
This time, I'm going to make him
fall in love like he's never fallen before.
Well now, this is fancy.
Sorry I kept you waiting.
S-Sara?
Is that really you?
It is.
I'm so glad I get to see you again.
S-so am I!
I never expected you to invite me out like this.
Here's your order.
Whoa, this is my favorite!
Really? Me too!
Please, enjoy.
That's weird.
My chest feels so tight.
So, I picked up a new hobby recently.
My dad is really into collecting records, you see.
Could this be destiny at work?
We like all the same foods,
and the records she's listing off are all so good,
I would kill to get my hands on them!
And on top of that,
she's doing that little head tilt thing I love!
Now, I see how pretty her skin is.
It makes me want to protect her.
God, she's so cute!
H-here's an idea.
After this, would you be interested in
stopping back at my place for a nightcap?
Oh, but...
Come on, just one drink?
That sounds nice, but...
But?
I do have one condition.
Of course, anything you ask!
Then, could you tell me the truth about
everything you've done up until now...
Tarik Pupke?
H-how do you know that name?!
You're a conman, aren't you?
N-no.
That's not it.
That's not what's happening here!
This... This is how I really feel!
Fine.
I'll tell you everything.
I guess all's well that ends well,
but how could you be sure that
following your directions
would be enough to take down Tarik?
Because I looked into his heart.
I know that man's desires like the back of my hand.
All I had to do was match that up with Sara's charm,
and it was a done deal.
Would you like me to tell you why
I washed out of my academy?
It was because I had relations with too many people.
Male faculty, local men, even some of
the other girls at my academy...
Damn...
There's this spy I admire.
In order to become like her,
I trained ceaselessly to be able to charm,
entice, and manipulate people.
If I bring my full talents to bear,
seducing some petty con artist is child's play.
When it comes to matters of love,
I'm the best in the game.
And that's everything.
B-but meeting you has inspired me
to turn over a new leaf!
That's the truth, I swear!
My feelings for you are real!
So, please-
I'm sorry, but life isn't that easy.
I'm going to give this to the police.
This is for all those girls who weren't able
to get fraud charges to stick.
You tricked me?!
Turnabout is fair play.
Now, goodbye.
H-hold on-
Don't you lay a finger on her.
Thank you, Tarik.
Even though it was just for a moment,
you fell in love with me.
Thanks to you, I have my confidence back.
But the thing is,
there's already a man in my life far lovelier than you.
U-um, I thought the plan was to have Miss Grete
come pick me up while crossdressing.
Thea gave me a basic rundown of the situation
and asked me to step in.
Ah, I see.
Oh, s-sorry, your arm...
Go ahead and leave them linked.
Pretending to be lovers is in our
interests at the moment.
O-okay.
I'm so embarrassed.
I let myself get all worked up thinking that
I might get to fall in love someday.
You have nothing to be ashamed of.
It's only natural for someone your age
to take an interest in romance.
In fact, why don't we hit the town?
I apologize that you'll have to settle for me
playing the part of the boyfriend,
but I'll do my best to take the lead
and show you a good time.
That way, you’ll know that you don’t have
anything to be afraid of the next time you feel
ready to have another go at falling in love.
Let's have a magnificent evening together.
Yes, sir!
Good boy!
My golden days are finally here!
Tarik was arrested again on
charges of suspected fraud.
Plus, his old victims have filed
civil cases against him, too.
He's finally getting the comeuppance he deserves!
You nailed it like always, Sis!
Good job!
Hey, don't forget about all the work
my homemade aphrodisiac put in!
No one but Thea coulda pull this plan off.
Were you all surprised to find out that I
can make stimulants and intoxicants
I'll follow you to the ends of the earth, Master.
on top of just paralytics?
Leave it to me.
You totally were, weren't you?
Today, I've come up with a plan
That's right! It's your girl!
that will finally let us take down Teach.
The Republic's hidden genius is right here! Among you!
This plan revolves around an outfit!
No matter how fierce the foe is, as soon as I get involved,
An outfit?
I rain judgement down upon them like it's nothing!
As soon as I saw, I said to myself, this is it!
If we want to defeat him, this is how we're going to do it!
Go on, praise me more!
Don't worry, I'll be wearing one too.
Teach will go down before he knows what hit him!
So, what's the deal?
Why don't Thea's seduction attempts work on you?
Her seduction is all based around first locking eyes
with her target and peering into their heart.
Ah, and she can't pull that off against you.
Exactly.
Still, I'm not quite sure how I should handle her.
Her attempts have been getting kind of extreme,
and it's starting to become a problem.
Hey, don't ask me.
Do pardon the intrusion.
I've brought you some tea.
I don't understand why you're wearing that thing.
Go on, Grete.
Now's your chance!
Rabbits' mating season is said to last the entire year,
so my outfit symbolizes the way that I'm ready
and prepared to accept men at any time.
I feel as though you've misunderstood my question.
Come on, Boss.
I'm ready and prepared to accept you at any time!
Hey, sorry to butt in...
Monika?
...but can I say something in Klaus's place?
Pretty sure that's not your size.
WHY?!